jeevan4u.com 2008-12-16

# Jeevan4u.com Privacy Policy

| Our Commitment to privacy  
---  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.   
The Information we collect  
  
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on jeevan4u.com. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

Name   
Address   
Email address  
Phone number (etc.)   
  
The way we use information  
  
  * We do not share your personal information and the information you provide about someone else with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete the service requested. 
  * We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 
  * Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

Our commitment to Data security   
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.   
Our commitment to children's privacy  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13.   
How to contact us  
  
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please mail us at   

| 

|   
---  
|  | Web Directory  
---  
Arts | Automobile | Books | Business | Charitable | Computers | Actors | Actress | Education |   
Entertainment | Fashion | Festivals | Forums | Friendship | Greeting Cards | Health | Hotels | Images | Jobs | Matrimonial | Movies | Music | News-Media | Personal | Real Estate | Christmas Cards | Search Engines | Spirituality  | Sports | Textiles | Tourism | Wallpapers | Web Directories  | Regional | Website Submission | Sponsored Links | Advertisements | Mail us |   
Models  
Models Photo | Justin | Kiran | Tito | Dilip | Abid Sait | Praveen Kumar VN | Jentil | Rizal Riyaz | Thomas Sebastian | Rajeev | Deepan | Georgy | Sudheer | Prasanth Babu | Abhilash | Alvin | Praveen Kumar PJ | Hari | Bigil | Nippy | Praveen | Santhosh | Binu | Ullas | Prem | Cyril |   
Kerala Tourism  
Kerala | Alappuzha | Calicut | Cochin | Ernakulam | Fortkochi | Idukki | Kovalam | Pathanamthitta | Thiruvananthapuram | Varkala |   
Babies World  
Babies World | Baby Boy Names starts with A,B,C,D | E,F,G,H,I | J,K,L,M,N | O,P,Q,R | S | Baby Boy Names starts with T,U,V | W,X,Y,Z | Girl Names starts with A,B,C,D | E,F,G,H,I |  
Baby Girl Names starts with J,K,L,M | N,O,P,Q,R | S | T,U,V | W,X,Y,Z | Baby Photos |   
Greeting Cards  
Birthday cards | Frirendship cards | Love cards | Valentine cards | Deepavali cards | Ramadan cards | Christmas cards | NewYear | Easter cards | Vishu cards | Onam cards |   
Quotes  
Achievement quotes | Beauty quotes | Birthday quotes | Discipline quotes | Failure quotes | Friendship quotes | Happiness quotes | Heart quotes | Health quotes | Humour quotes | Life quotes | Love quotes | Peace | Romantic quotes | Sadness quotes | Sports quotes | Strength quotes | Teacher quotes | Valentine quotes | Wedding quotes | Women Quotes |   
Wedding Albums  
Album | Santhosh Nagils | Joby Jis | Vipindas Manjusha | Binoy Simi | Jiby Deepti | Roshan Veena | Robin Dhanya | Victor Ligiya | Nikhil Raji | Sudeep Aparna | Bibin Jisha | Savio Nimy | Saban Bipitha | Vipin Leena | Shine Shinu | Pranam Remy | Jijo Magin | Happy Smitha | Arun Ravi Nisha | Suraj Remya | Jobin Jofy | Manoj Anu | Sajin Teena | Abhilash Archana | Rajesh Diana | Jose Swapna | Nandakumar Remya | Santhosh Asha | Anish Neema | Lijo Tintu | Prakash Neethu | Pradeep Deepti | Binu Beena | Sijo Reena | Shibu Simy | Sudheesh Saritha | Krishnaprasad Vincy | Baiju Ambily | Bijo Roselin | UnniKrishnan Greeshma | Ajish Annsophia | Shiju Vimcy | Anup Ambili | Sajit Julie | Pradeep Pavol | Binu Nisha | Aby Anupama | Tijo Shiji | Toby Carolin | Aneesh Priya | Manoj Lakshmi | Ajeesh Salvia | George Bitty | Biju Smitha | Doctor Shiju Tany | Joseph Kala | Justine Anitha | Justine Nija | Boben Tina | Raju Eimee | Soji Betsy | Dilip Rinu | Jinu Jifi | Rajesh Litha | Varghese Sapna | Sebastian Rose | Shajeev Dhanya | Rajeev Sonia | Arun Sheeba | Krishnaraj Radhika | Bijo Rincy  | Sumesh Maya | Maju Anu | Jayan Bindu | Robin Biby | Joemon Aiby | Byju Lysa | Rajeev Sugathakumari | Manoj Manju | Renjith Swapna | Shiju Ruby |   
Movies  
RedChillies | Kurukshetra | Lolly Pop | Thirakatha | Adayalangal | Aakashagopuram | Madambi | Kuttysrank | Parunthu | Mizhikal Sakshi | Mayakazhcha | Magic Lamp | Positive | Shakespeare MA Malayalam | Pachamarathanalil | Veruthe Oru Bharya | Twenty20 | Parthan kanda paralokam | Annan Thampi | Innathe Chinthavishayam | De ingotu nokiye | Mulla | Laptop | Jubliee | Raudram | Rock N Roll  | College Kumaran | Nasrani | Chocolate | Ore Kadal | Ali bhai | Heartbeats  | Kalchilambu | Mission 90 days | Hallo | July 4 | Nivedhyam | Kalchilambu | Pazhassiraja | Anamika | Vandemataram | Paradesi | Arabikatha | Kichamani mba | Sooriyan | Black cat | Nadiya kollapeta rathri | Veeralipattu | Chotta Mumbai | Bigb | Baba Kalyani | BharathChandran IPS  
Film Stars  
Film Stars | Tom Cruise | John Abraham | Mammootty | Mohanlal | Suresh Gopi | Amirkhan | Ajith | Vikram | Jayaram | Surya | Dileep | Kavya | Trisha | Gopika | Nayanthara | Asin | Prithviraj | Meera Jasmine | Jyothika | Bhavana | Navya Nair | Mamta Mohandas | Vimalaraman | Sindhu Menon | Sneha | Karthika | Samvritha Sunil | Lakshmi | Priyamani | Renuka Menon | Padmapriya | Rani | Nikitha | Aishwarya Rai |   
Finland Scrapbook  
Rotary Team | Kemi | Tornio | Rovaniemi | Sodankyla | Ivalo | Kemijarvi | Kuusamo | Oulu | Helsinki | Finland Geography | Map | Flag | Currency | Tourism | People | Language | Universities | Shopping | Vodka | Music | Finnish Design | Climate | Smitha |   
Holiday Tours  
Tenmala | Contour Jungle Resorts | Kuttikkanam | Wagamon | Idukki | Honeymoon Tour Packages  
Christmas  
About Christmas | Birth of Jesus | Gifts to Jesus | Santa Claus | Christmas Cribs | Christmas Cards | Jesus, the Message \- Bro. Binu Chollackal, Brazil   
Top Engineering Colleges  
National Institute of Technology Calicut | Rajiv Gandhi Institute of Technology Pampady | Government Engineering College Thrissur | College of Engineering Thiruvananthapuram |   
Mar Athanasius Engg. College Kothamangalam  
Malayalam Poems - Kavithakal  
Verpadu | Hey pushpame | Daivasandhesham | Maranam | Yathramangalam (Sarath Babu)  
Flash Greetings + Message  
Vishu Greetings Flash Movie 1 | Vishu Movie 2 | Christmas - NewYear Movie | Easter Lent Message | Diwali English Movie | [St. valentines day malayalam Movie 1](http://jeevan4u.com/valentine/) | [Valentine Movie 2](http://jeevan4u.com/valentine/movie.aspx) | Onam Greeting Movie 1 | Onam Greeting Movie 2  
Special Moments  
Royce Rimi Tomy Marriage | KishorSatya Pooja Marriage | Nikhil Remya Marriage | Naren + Manju wedding | Srikanth + Vandana wedding | Selvaraghavan + Sonia Agarwal wedding | Surya + Jyothika wedding | Reception contest | Marian ignite 2007 | Onam Gettogether 2005 | Onam Gettogether2006 | Tiruvonam Photos 2005 | Onam Photos 2006   
  
|  |
